Hello everyone and welcome to EnglishPod.
大家好，欢迎收听EnglishPod。
My name is Marco.
我是Marco。
My name is Katrin and we've got an upper intermediate level lesson for you guys today.
我是Katrin，今天我们为大家准备了一节中高级课程。
This one is all about a crime scene.
这节课全是关于犯罪现场的。
That's right.
没错。
So we are going to be at a crime scene.
所以我们要去一个犯罪现场。
We are with the police officers and we're going to take a look at some very, very interesting
我们和警察一起，会看到一些非常非常有趣
and specific vocab to like police and a crime and all that.
且专业的词汇，跟警察、犯罪之类的有关。
That's right.
没错。
So if you are a fan of the TV show CSI or you like some of these investigation police
所以如果你是电视剧《犯罪现场调查》的粉丝，或者你喜欢那些调查警察
work TV shows, this is a lesson for you.
工作的电视剧，这节课就是为你准备的。
That's right.
没错。
So why don't we go and listen to the dialogue for the first time.
那我们不如先听一遍对话吧。
All right, Officer McGraw, give it to me straight.
好的，McGraw警官，直说吧。
What are we looking at here?
我们这里看到了什么？
Detective McGee, I'm glad to see you.
McGee探长，很高兴见到你。
We could sure use your expertise on this one.
这个案子我们确实需要你的专业意见。
It's a break in, but nothing seems to have been stolen.
是一起入室盗窃案，但似乎什么都没被偷。
We received a call from the Bear family at around 1030 this morning.
我们今天上午10点30分左右接到了Bear一家的报警电话。
They'd gone out for a walk before breakfast and came home to this mess.
他们早餐前出去散步，回家就看到了这团乱。
Broken chairs and porridge all over the place.
椅子坏了，粥洒得到处都是。
Apparently Mama Bear had made the porridge a little too hot, you see.
显然，熊妈妈把粥煮得有点太烫了，你看。
They were waiting for it to cool down.
他们正在等它凉下来。
Okay then, let's start examining the evidence.
好吧，那我们开始检查证据吧。
Have the forensics team been in yet?
法医小组来过了吗？
Yes sir.
是的，长官。
We found some fingerprints on the bowls and are analyzing them back at the lab as we speak.
我们在碗上发现了一些指纹，现在正在实验室里分析。
Hopefully they will be able to identify the burglar soon.
希望他们能很快识别出那个闯入者。
Hmm.
嗯。
Aha!
啊哈！
What's this?
这是什么？
A strand of golden hair.
一缕金色的头发。
This is a very important piece of trace evidence, McGraw.
这是一条非常重要的微量证据，麦格劳。
It tells me the suspect has long golden hair and very few men have long golden hair.
这告诉我嫌疑人有长长的金发，而很少有男人有长长的金发。
So our criminal could be a woman.
所以我们的罪犯可能是个女人。
A woman?
一个女人？
Was she working alone?
她是单独作案吗？
Did she have an accomplice?
她有同伙吗？
An accomplice?
同伙？
No.
没有。
No, McGraw.
不，麦格劳。
She was definitely working alone.
她肯定是单独行动的。
See here, there are footprints in the porridge.
你看，粥里有脚印。
Here on the floor, small footprints.
地板上也有，小小的脚印。
This tells me that our suspect is small and could possibly be a child.
这说明我们的嫌疑人体型很小，可能是个孩子。
A child?
一个孩子？
Surely not, sir.
肯定不是，长官。
We must follow the clues, McGraw.
我们必须跟着线索走，麦格劳。
The evidence doesn't lie.
证据不会说谎。
Now let's reconstruct the crime.
现在我们来还原犯罪现场。
The suspect came in, sat in each chair breaking the smallest one into little pieces.
嫌疑人进来后，每把椅子都坐了一遍，把最小的那把坐碎了。
Next, the porridge.
接下来是粥。
She obviously tried to eat it and because it was so hot, she dropped it on the floor,
她显然想尝一口，但因为太烫，就掉在了地上，
making this mess.
弄得一团糟。
Hmm.
嗯。
Interesting.
有意思。
These footprints seem to lead upstairs.
这些脚印似乎通向楼上。
McGraw, did your officers clear the scene?
麦格劳，你的人搜查过现场了吗？
Well, there was no one down here.
呃，楼下没人。
Maybe we forgot to check upstairs.
也许我们忘了检查楼上。
Hey, what's with all the noise?
嘿，这噪音是怎么回事？
I'm trying to sleep up here.
我在这儿想睡觉呢。
There she is.
她在那儿。
Get her.
抓住她。
Alright, we're back.
好了，我们回来了。
So a lot of interesting phrases there.
刚才有不少有趣的短语。
They are obviously investigating a break-in.
他们显然在调查一起入室盗窃案。
Okay a break-in, yeah.
对，入室盗窃案。
So someone broke into this family's house.
所以有人闯进了这户人家。
So they have to investigate the evidence and some of the things that were left behind.
所以他们得调查证据和留下的线索。
So now why don't we take a look on Language Takeaway, some of the specific words they
现在我们来看看“语言要点”部分，一些他们用到的具体词汇。
used.
用到的。
Language Takeaway.
语言要点。
Alright the first word that we have is forensics, the forensics team.
好的，第一个词是“法医”，法医团队。
Forensics team.
法医团队。
So a forensics team is a team at a police department or police station that studies
法医团队是警察局或派出所里研究犯罪后遗留物品的团队。
the things that are left behind after a crime.
好的，这个团队会去收集证据。
Alright so that team goes and collects the evidence.
你可以检查头发、指纹或脚印之类的东西。
So you could look at hair or fingerprints or footprints, things like that.
法医团队有点像拼图团队，试图找出线索。
A forensics team is kind of like a team that puts together puzzle pieces trying to figure
out what the story was.
弄清楚事情的来龙去脉。
So as you said, the TV show CSI, the whole show revolves around, follows a group of forensic
所以就像你说的，电视剧《CSI》整部剧都围绕着一群法医展开。
scientists who go to crime scenes and look at blood and different pieces of evidence
这些科学家会前往犯罪现场，检查血迹和各种遗留的证据。
that are left behind.
这些证据是现场留下的。
Very cool.
非常酷。
So one piece of evidence that a forensics team might look at is a fingerprint.
法医团队可能会检查的一种证据是指纹。
That's right, a fingerprint or in the dialogue we found fingerprints, the plural form.
没错，指纹，或者像对话里说的“fingerprints”，是复数形式。
Okay so for example, if you go to a police station because the police think that you
好的，举个例子，如果你因为警察怀疑你犯了罪而去警察局。
have committed a crime, the police will take your fingerprints.
警察会提取你的指纹。
That means they'll put your finger, that means they'll put your fingers into ink and they
也就是说，他们会把你的手指放进墨水里。
will make you push your fingers onto a piece of paper to see what your fingers look like.
然后让你把手指按在纸上，看看你的指纹是什么样子的。
That's right.
没错。
So our fingerprints have a unique pattern.
所以我们的指纹有独特的纹路。
Everyone has different fingerprints.
每个人的指纹都不同。
There are no two fingerprints alike in the world, right?
世界上没有两个完全相同的指纹，对吧？
Right, so it's kind of like a form of identification.
对，所以这有点像一种身份识别方式。
Very good.
非常好。
That's right, so that is your fingerprint.
没错，这就是你的指纹。
So moving on, we talked about fingerprints and the scientists who are investigating the
接下来，我们聊了指纹和调查犯罪现场的科学家。
crime scene and they are talking about a very important piece of trace evidence.
他们正在讨论一种非常重要的微量证据。
Okay well let's look first at the second word there.
好的，我们先来看第二个词。
We've got the word evidence.
我们看到了“evidence”这个词。
So evidence is something that is usually physical like a piece of clothing or hair that can
“evidence”通常是指像衣物或头发这类实物，可以用来
be used against someone when we're trying to prove that they have committed a crime.
在试图证明某人犯罪时作为指控他们的依据。
Right, so for example a weapon or fingerprints, all that is evidence.
对，比如武器或指纹，这些都是证据。
Okay so Marco, what's the difference between evidence and trace evidence?
好的，Marco，那“evidence”和“trace evidence”有什么区别？
Well as you notice you have the specific word there, trace.
嗯，你注意到这里有个特定的词“trace”。
And to trace means to follow or to connect, right?
“trace”的意思是追踪或关联，对吧？
So what you're doing here is you're taking this evidence to follow or connect the person
所以这里你是在利用这些证据来追踪或关联那个
that committed the crime.
犯罪的人。
So for example, fingerprints lets you know who committed the crime.
比如，指纹能让你知道是谁犯了罪。
Okay, or maybe if you have blood you can find out who did this crime.
好的，或者如果有血迹，你也能找出是谁干的。
Right.
对。
But what about like a broken window?
但像破窗户这样的呢？
Well that's just evidence.
那只是证据。
It just lets you know how the crime was committed, maybe how they got into the house.
它只能让你知道犯罪是怎么发生的，比如他们是怎么进房子的。
But not who did it.
但不能指出是谁干的。
Okay, so trace evidence helps you connect the crime to the person who committed the
好的，所以“trace evidence”能帮你把犯罪和犯罪的人
crime.
联系起来。
And well moving on, we found that very important piece of trace evidence which was a piece
接着往下说，我们发现了一个非常重要的微量证据，那是一根
of or a strand of golden hair and the police officer said, well this tells me that the
金色的头发，警官说，这告诉我
suspect has long golden hair.
嫌疑人有一头金色长发。
So a suspect.
所以是“嫌疑人”。
Okay this word, it looks exactly the same as the word to suspect.
好的，这个词看起来和动词“怀疑”一模一样。
But be careful because we say these two words in different ways.
但要注意，这两个词的发音方式不同。
So to suspect, that's a verb.
所以“怀疑”是动词。
That's right.
没错。
So I suspect Marco did it.
所以我怀疑是马可干的。
So that means I think or I imagine.
那意味着我认为或我猜想。
Right, whereas a suspect, a noun, a suspect is a person.
对，而“嫌疑人”是名词，指的是一个人。
So the person who we think or the person who the police think committed a crime.
也就是我们或警方认为可能犯罪的人。
Okay.
好的。
So for example, we're talking about some trace evidence like long blonde hair.
比如，我们刚才提到一些微量证据，比如金色长发。
That means the suspect is probably a woman and is probably blonde.
那意味着嫌疑人很可能是个女性，而且可能是金发。
Very good.
非常好。
And it's interesting that you use the verb to suspect and a suspect all because you're
有趣的是，你用了动词“怀疑”和名词“嫌疑人”，因为都表示
not sure yet.
还不确定。
So this person may have committed the crime or may not.
所以这个人可能犯了罪，也可能没有。
That's right.
没错。
So we have to wait until the trial.
所以我们得等到审判。
We have to wait until we prove this person is guilty before we can say that they actually
我们必须等到证明这个人有罪之后，才能说他们确实
committed the crime.
犯了罪。
Very good.
很好。
Okay.
好的。
And well, you have a suspect and usually you also have somebody who is an accomplice to
嗯，你有一个嫌疑人，通常还有一个同谋，与
the crime or to the suspect.
犯罪或嫌疑人有关。
Okay.
好的。
So a suspect, as we said, is a person.
所以嫌疑人，就像我们说的，是一个人。
It's a noun.
它是一个名词。
So is an accomplice.
同谋也是。
So accomplice is a suspect's helper.
所以同谋是嫌疑人的帮手。
Right.
对。
So basically if you're robbing a bank and I wait outside in the car, right, while you're
所以基本上，如果你在抢银行，而我在外面车里等着，对吧，当你
robbing the bank, then I am an accomplice.
抢银行时，我就是同谋。
That's right.
没错。
And under most laws, you could be sentenced to jail.
根据大多数法律，你可能会被判入狱。
Right.
对。
So the accomplice usually doesn't commit the crime, right?
所以同谋通常不直接犯罪，对吧？
You robbed the bank, but I just waited outside in the car to drive you out.
你抢了银行，但我只是在外面车里等着开车带你走。
So I didn't rob the bank.
所以我没有抢银行。
Right.
对。
But sometimes accomplices do also have guns and shoot people or knives.
但有时候同伙也会拿枪或刀伤人。
So an accomplice is basically just the helper of the criminal, but they can get in trouble
所以同伙基本上就是罪犯的帮手，但他们也会惹上麻烦，
too.
也会。
Right.
对。
So basically it's a person that helps out and knows about the crime, but didn't tell
所以基本上就是那种帮忙、知情犯罪，但没有向警方举报的人。
the police about it.
没有向警方举报。
Exactly.
没错。
That's a really important aspect.
那是一个非常重要的方面。
Okay.
好的。
So a lot of interesting words there all related to crimes.
所以这里有很多与犯罪相关的有趣词汇。
Why don't we move on now to a couple of different phrases that we have prepared for you on Fluency
我们不如继续看看在Fluency Builder上为你准备的一些不同短语吧。
Builder.
Builder。
Fluency Builder.
Fluency Builder。
Okay.
好的。
I like this.
我喜欢这个。
This first phrase, it's a phrase you might hear a lot actually in police shows.
第一个短语，你在警匪剧里可能经常听到。
Give it to me straight.
直说吧。
Actually, also you can use it when you're just talking to someone and they're like hesitant,
实际上，当你跟别人聊天，对方显得犹豫不决时，也可以用这个说法。
right?
对吧？
Like, I don't know how to tell you this, but...
比如，“我不知道该怎么跟你说，但是……”
I'm not so sure.
“我不太确定。”
I don't think you're going to like what I have to say.
“我觉得你不会喜欢我要说的话。”
So I can just say, okay, come on, just give it to me straight.
所以我就可以说，“好吧，来吧，直接告诉我吧。”
Okay.
好的。
I don't like your shirt.
“我不喜欢你的衬衫。”
No, I'm just kidding.
不，我开玩笑的。
It's a nice shirt.
这件衬衫不错。
But what you're basically asking for is the person to say, be honest with me.
但你实际上是在要求对方说，“对我诚实点。”
Be direct.
直接点。
Straight can mean both of those things, honest or straightforward or quick.
“Straight”可以指这两件事：诚实、直截了当或快速。
You don't want someone to go around and around and say lots of different things.
你不想让别人绕来绕去，说一大堆不同的话。
So I guess, yeah, that does make sense.
所以我想，嗯，这确实说得通。
Give it to me straight maybe comes from straightforward.
“直接告诉我”可能来源于“直截了当”。
So to be straightforward is to not hesitate to just say something directly and honestly.
所以“直截了当”就是不犹豫，直接、诚实地说出某事。
Exactly.
没错。
Okay.
好的。
So moving on to our next phrase, McGraw is talking about the bulls and he said, well,
那么接下来看我们的下一个短语，麦格劳在谈论公牛时说，嗯，
they are analyzing them back at the lab as we speak.
就在我们说话的这会儿，他们正在实验室里分析那些公牛。
As we speak.
就在我们说话的这会儿。
Okay.
好的。
So this is actually a phrase that refers to time.
所以这其实是一个指代时间的短语。
So in this instance, what he's basically saying is right now.
在这个例子中，他基本上是在说“现在”。
They're being analyzed right now or in this moment.
它们正在被分析，就在现在或此刻。
So it's a way of indicating that something is happening at this very moment.
所以这是一种表示某事正在此刻发生的方式。
Exactly.
没错。
So I could say, did you know that the president is giving a speech as we speak?
所以我可以这样说：你知道吗，总统就在我们说话的这会儿正在发表演讲？
Okay.
好的。
So that means the president is talking right now.
那就意味着总统现在正在讲话。
Exactly.
没错。
As we speak.
就在我们说话的这会儿。
Okay.
好的。
Very good phrase.
非常好的短语。
Now, moving on to our third phrase, Detective McGee was talking about reconstructing the
现在，来看我们的第三个短语，麦吉侦探在谈论重构
crime.
犯罪现场。
He said, let's reconstruct the crime.
他说，我们来重构犯罪现场。
Okay.
好的。
So I don't know if any of you watch these crime TV shows like Dexter or CSI.
我不知道你们有没有看过像《嗜血法医》或《犯罪现场调查》这样的犯罪电视剧。
This is my favorite part because they tell you exactly what they believe happened.
这是我最喜欢的部分，因为他们会准确告诉你他们认为发生了什么。
So to reconstruct means to build again or to recreate, to create again.
所以“reconstruct”的意思是重建或重新创造，再次创造。
So basically they start at the beginning and they pretend to follow what happened during
基本上，他们从开头开始，假装跟随犯罪过程中发生的事情，
the crime.
犯罪过程。
So that's basically the verb to reconstruct, to rebuild, recreate.
所以这就是动词“reconstruct”的意思，重建、重新创造。
Okay.
好的。
Reconstruct the crime.
重建犯罪现场。
Very good.
非常好。
And what about our last phrase?
那我们的最后一个短语呢？
Okay.
好的。
So our last phrase is again, a very typical police phrase.
所以我们的最后一个短语又是一个非常典型的警察用语。
We hear this a lot when there's been a crime or on TV when they're talking about the scene
我们经常在发生犯罪时或电视上谈论犯罪现场时听到这个，
of the crime, that means the place where the crime happened.
犯罪现场，就是犯罪发生的地方。
And the police say we need to clear the scene or did the officers clear the scene?
警察会说“我们需要清理现场”或“警察清理现场了吗？”
So to clear means to empty out.
所以“clear”的意思是清空。
Right.
对。
But they're not talking about emptying out the evidence or removing everything from the
但他们说的不是清空证据或把房子里所有东西都搬走，
house.
房子。
They're just saying to remove people, right?
他们只是说把人清走，对吧？
Right.
没错。
Or obstructions.
或者障碍物。
Exactly.
正是。
So a police officer would want to make all the people go away.
所以警察会想让所有人都离开。
Well, because you don't want people stepping on the evidence or maybe putting their fingerprints
嗯，因为你不希望有人踩到证据，或者把他们的指纹
all over the place.
弄得到处都是。
Right.
没错。
So it's very important that the officers, the police officers clear the scene so that
所以警察清理现场非常重要，这样
they can start their investigation.
他们才能开始调查。
Right.
没错。
Very good.
很好。
A lot of interesting phrases there.
那里有很多有趣的短语。
I think we should go back.
我觉得我们应该回去。
Why don't we listen to the dialogue for the last time and we'll come back and talk a little
我们最后再听一遍对话，然后回来再聊一聊
bit more this.
这个。
And we'll come back and talk a little bit more about this really interesting topic.
然后我们回来再聊一聊这个非常有趣的话题。
All right, Officer McGraw, give it to me straight.
好的，麦格劳警官，直说吧。
What are we looking at here?
我们这里看到了什么？
Detective McGee, glad to see you.
麦基侦探，很高兴见到你。
We could sure use your expertise on this one.
我们这次真需要你的专业知识。
It's a break in, but nothing seems to have been stolen.
是入室盗窃，但似乎什么都没被偷。
We received a call from the Bear family at around 1030 this morning.
我们今天早上大约10点30分接到熊家的电话。
They'd gone out for a walk before breakfast and came home to this mess.
他们早餐前出去散步，回家就看到了这乱摊子。
Broken chairs and porridge all over the place.
椅子碎了，粥洒得到处都是。
Apparently Mama Bear had made the porridge a little too hot, you see.
显然熊妈妈把粥煮得有点太烫了，你看。
They were waiting for it to cool down.
他们正在等它凉下来。
Okay, then let's start examining the evidence.
好的，那我们开始检查证据吧。
Have the forensics team been in yet?
法医团队来过了吗？
Yes, sir.
是的，长官。
They found some fingerprints on the bowls and are analyzing them back at the lab as
他们在碗上发现了一些指纹，现在正在实验室分析，
we speak.
就在我们说话的时候。
Hopefully they will be able to identify the burglar soon.
希望他们能很快识别出那个窃贼。
Hmm.
嗯。
Aha!
啊哈！
What's this?
这是什么？
A strand of golden hair.
一缕金发。
This is a very important piece of trace evidence, McGraw.
这是一条非常重要的微量证据，麦格劳。
It tells me the suspect has long golden hair, and very few men have long golden hair.
它告诉我嫌疑人有长长的金发，而很少有男人有长长的金发。
So our criminal could be a woman.
所以我们的罪犯可能是个女人。
A woman?
一个女人？
Was she working alone?
她是单独作案吗？
Did she have an accomplice?
她有同伙吗？
An accomplice?
同伙？
No.
不。
No, McGraw.
不，麦格劳。
She was definitely working alone.
她肯定是单独作案。
See, here there are footprints in the porridge.
看，这里有粥里的脚印。
Here on the floor, small footprints.
地板上这里，小脚印。
This tells me that our suspect is small, and could possibly be a child.
这告诉我我们的嫌疑人个子小，可能是个孩子。
A child?
一个孩子？
Surely not, sir.
肯定不是，长官。
We must follow the clues, McGraw.
我们必须遵循线索，麦格劳。
The evidence doesn't lie.
证据不会说谎。
Now let's reconstruct the crime.
现在我们来重建犯罪现场。
The suspect came in, sat in each chair breaking the smallest one into little pieces.
嫌疑人进来，坐在每把椅子上，把最小的那把椅子弄成了碎片。
Next, the porridge, she obviously tried to eat it, and because it was so hot she dropped
接着，粥，她显然想尝一尝，但因为太烫，她把它
it on the floor, making this mess.
掉在了地上，弄得一团糟。
Hmm, interesting.
嗯，有意思。
These footprints seem to lead upstairs.
这些脚印似乎通向楼上。
McGraw, did your officers clear the scene?
麦格劳，你的警官清理过现场吗？
Well, there was no one down here.
嗯，楼下没人。
Maybe we forgot to check upstairs.
也许我们忘了检查楼上。
Hey, what's with all the noise?
嘿，吵什么吵？
I'm trying to sleep up here.
我在这儿睡觉呢。
There she is!
她在那儿！
Get her!
抓住她！
So you mentioned a couple of different shows, such as Dexter and CSI.
所以你提到了几部不同的剧，比如《嗜血法医》和《犯罪现场调查》。
Do you watch any of these shows?
你看这些剧吗？
I do.
我看。
I'm a big fan of Dexter.
我是《嗜血法医》的忠实粉丝。
And Dexter, as you know, works at a police station in Miami.
而《嗜血法医》，如你所知，在迈阿密的警察局工作。
His character is in forensics.
他的角色是法医。
He analyzes blood.
他分析血液。
Right, he's like a blood expert.
对，他像个血液专家。
But it's interesting because he is actually, he commits crimes himself.
但有趣的是，他实际上自己也在犯罪。
So he uses his knowledge to help him to not get caught.
所以他利用自己的知识来帮助自己不被抓住。
Right, so he's both a criminal and he's a police officer.
对，所以他既是罪犯又是警察。
But he's kind of like a superhero criminal, right?
但他有点像超级英雄罪犯，对吧？
Because he doesn't kill for fun or pleasure.
因为他杀人不是为了好玩或快感。
He just takes out people who kind of deserve it, right?
他只是除掉那些罪有应得的人，对吧？
Yes, but he does kind of do it for pleasure because he's obsessed.
是的，但他确实有点为了乐趣而这么做，因为他痴迷于此。
He can't not kill.
他无法不杀人。
So instead of killing good people, he decides he will only ever kill bad people.
所以，他不杀好人，而是决定只杀坏人。
It's a really good show.
这是一部非常好的剧。
I've watched a couple of episodes and it's very, very good.
我看了几集，非常非常好看。
The same as CSI.
和《CSI》一样。
There are a couple of different versions.
有几个不同的版本。
There's CSI Miami, New York, and Las Vegas.
有《CSI：迈阿密》、《纽约》和《拉斯维加斯》。
But my favorite is Las Vegas.
但我最喜欢的是《拉斯维加斯》。
It's very, very good.
非常非常好看。
And also Law & Order.
还有《法律与秩序》。
I've watched a couple of episodes of Law & Order.
我看了几集《法律与秩序》。
It's pretty good.
挺不错的。
Yeah, they often talk about forensics because they have both parts.
是啊，他们经常谈论法医学，因为这部剧有两部分。
They have the police part and the law part with the lawyers who have to use the evidence
有警察部分，还有法律部分，涉及律师必须使用证据
in court.
在法庭上。
Very interesting.
非常有趣。
And there's also, well, forensic scientists, they take a look at the evidence.
还有，嗯，法医科学家，他们会检查证据。
But I think also they examine the body back at the morgue, right?
但我觉得他们也会在停尸房检查尸体，对吧？
That's right.
没错。
They look at the body to find out what happened to the body.
他们检查尸体，找出尸体发生了什么。
This is all a part of reconstructing the crime.
这都是重建犯罪过程的一部分。
So this person is also sometimes called a coroner, right?
所以这个人有时也被称为验尸官，对吧？
Okay, the person who analyzes the body.
好的，就是分析尸体的人。
It's pretty scary though if you think about it, having to analyze a body.
不过想想看，分析尸体还是挺吓人的。
I think you have to be very experienced.
我觉得你必须非常有经验。
It's a very interesting...
这是一个非常有趣的……
I don't even know how somebody becomes a forensic scientist, for example.
我甚至不知道一个人是怎么成为法医科学家的，比如。
Do you study this in school?
你在学校学这个吗？
Oh, you can go to school for it.
哦，你可以去学校学这个。
Yeah, they have lots of forensic programs.
是啊，有很多法医学项目。
I think I saw on Discovery Channel, they have a reality TV show about forensic students
我想我在探索频道看过，有一个关于法医学学生的真人秀节目，
and they're actually taken to real crime scenes and then they get eliminated one by one.
他们被带到真实的犯罪现场，然后一个接一个被淘汰。
I'll have to look it up.
我得查查这个。
Well, I'm curious to know, have you ever heard of this before, forensic science or forensic
嗯，我很好奇，你以前听说过这个吗，法医学或法医
anthropology?
人类学？
There are lots of people who study this and who do this as a job.
有很多人学习这个，并以此为职业。
And if you're not interested in that, maybe you could tell us about what kind of crime
如果你对这个不感兴趣，也许你可以告诉我们你喜欢什么样的犯罪
drama TV shows you like, because we certainly love them here.
剧集，因为我们这里确实很喜欢。
Our website is EnglishPod.com.
我们的网站是EnglishPod.com。
All right, we'll see everyone there.
好了，我们会在那里见大家。
Bye.
再见。